(Amy:)and you stood at the rail
(Amy:)Googling the symptoms
of hypothermia?
(Sheldon:)We made one heck of a team, huh?
(Amy:)Whose bra is this?
(Sheldon:)It's not yours?
(Sheldon:)Oh, my.
(Sheldon:)How embarrassing for both of us.
(Amy:)It's Penny's.
(Sheldon:)Hey, you broke up with me.
(Sheldon:)It is none of your business
(Sheldon:)whose naked bosom I'm smooshing
around like pizza dough.
(Amy:)Good-bye.
(Scene:)Amy.
Amy. Amy.
(sighs)
(Sheldon:)Hmm. Tables work, too.
(Sheldon:)Good to know.
(Howard:)Ooh, brownies
for girls' night!
(Bernadette:)Hands off. I'm mad at you.
(sighs)
(Howard:)Look, I know it's
a lot of money,
(Howard:)but the guy at
the store said
(Howard:)in five to seven years,
it'll pay for itself.